# Habimana Eliane

Email: elianehabimana3@gmail.com | Tel: 0789484876 | Github: Elianehbmna

#### **Personal Statement**

An expert and skilled Full stack developer, captivated with coding, sharing my understanding with others and reading books. As a targeted and hardworking developer, I always deliver my work in good quality and additionally on-time.

## **Highlighted Software Applications**

Project Name: Ingabo Alpha- Full Stack Developer

**Year:** April 2020

Url:https://apkpure.com/ingabo-alpha/rw.alphacomputer.alphadefense

Ingabo alpha is an app that I developed for a company who mostly does things related to cybersecurity, the app I developed sells Bitdefender anti-viruses.

• Worked on the whole backend

Worked on the whole Frontend

**Project Name**: Moringa Automated help desk - Fullstack Developer

**Year:** November 2019

The project is a full-stack application which will help Moringa School students in their communication and also help them to share their knowledge in programming it is also a good way to study some of the programming languages. The project will help up to a hundred students in wecode for better learning experience.

• Worked on the Chatroom feature some of the technologies used (Django, Django-channels, Bootstrap, Postgres)

**Project Name**: mysquaremeters- UI/UX

**Year:** July 2021

Url:mysquaremeters.com

And some other confidential projects I worked on for a company for which I work.

Technical skills - Personal Skills - Digital Skills

Technical skills	Personal Skills	Digital Skills
Strong and experienced: PYTHON ,Flask ,Django ,Javascript,HTML , CSS,postgresql,mysql,powerb i,github,data analytics  Experienced: Angular, Java, Android,API integrations.	Problem Solving Team Work Time management	IT support Microsoft Word Microsoft PowerPoint excel G Suite Trello

# Languages

Languages	level
Kinyarwanda	Native language
French	Fluent
English	Fluent

# **Academic Qualifications**

# 1.College of Science and Technology(KIST)

2016-2020

Bachelor with honours in Computer and Software Engineering

### **Relevant Courses:**

- Embedded computer systems Engineering
- Network Security

- JAVA
- Digital Communication
- Android
- Software Project Management

### 2.Moringa School-WeCode

June 2019 - December 2019

Full-Stack Developer

#### **Relevant Courses:**

- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- Jquery
- Javascript
- Angular
- Python
- Flask
- Django

#### 3.University of Kigali

May 2022-Oct 2023

Ongoing masters degree in information technology

Relevant Courses:

- Project Management
- E-governance
- Software Architecture Design
- Cyber Security

## **Work Experience**

#### MYSQM Ltd

2020-present

Position:Software Developer

### • Bank of Kigali

2022-present

Position: Data Scientist

## **Professional Courses/Training**

## Resonate

2017

Theme:" leadership potential of women and girls"